Guide to the Campus Club Records, 1914-ongoing UA.28.01.0011
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Campus Club records
1914-ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Campus Club
UA.28.01.0011
24.5 Linear Feet
The Campus Club was founded in 1914 as a way for the wives of Duke faculty members to create a social community and to support the University through educational events. The collection contains documentation of Campus Club events, business meetings, and financial transactions, as well as scrapbooks, correspondence, clippings, and publications. The collection materials range in date from 1914 to ongoing.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Campus Club Records were received by the University Archives as a series of transfers.
Historical Note
From the Campus Club website: Since its founding in 1914, the purpose of Campus Club has been to promote knowledge of the goals and structures of Duke University, to increase communication and friendship within the university and community, as well as to extend a warm welcome to new members. The membership encompasses a unique grouping of all women affiliated with Duke University, including among others: Duke faculty women, wives/partners of faculty, staff members, women officers and administrators, Duke volunteers, alumnae and wives of alumni, and family of all eligible women.
Collection Overview
This collection contains a variety of materials pertaining to the history of the Campus Club. Primary contents include notebooks kept by executive board members, scrapbooks created by various committees, and records documenting the work of numerous groups within the Club. Addtional types of documentation contained within the collection are promotional materials, oral histories, publicity clippings, and membership records.
College teachers' spouses -- North Carolina -- Durham; Duke University. Campus Club; Duke University -- Faculty; Duke University -- Societies, etc.; Duke University. Newcomers' Club; Duke University -- Social life and customs
- Presidential Papers, 1952-1970 (Box 1)
- President's Handbook: Policy and Inventories, 1956-1988 (Box 1)
- President's Annual Reports, 1958-59 to 1976-1977 (Box 1)
- President's Annual Reports, 1958-59 to 1976-1977 (Box 1)
- President's Annual Reports, 1958-59 to 1976-1977 (Box 1)
- President's Handbook: Work Plan, Officers List, Bylaws, 1961-1989 (Box 1)
- President's Files, 1971-1978 (Box 1)
- President's Files, 1971-1978 (Box 1)
- President's Files, 1971-1978 (Box 1)
- President's Files, 1971-1978 (Box 1)
- President's Notes and Records, 1975-1976 and 1978-1979 (Box 1)
- President's Notes and Records, 1975-1976 and 1978-1979 (Box 1)
- President's Publication Notebook, 1975-1999 (Box 1)
- President's Publication Notebook, 1975-1999 (Box 1)
- President's Reports, 1977-1986 (Box 1)
- President's Papers, 1979-1981 (Box 1)
- President's Papers, 1979-1981 (Box 1)
- President's Papers, 1979-1981 (Box 2)
- President's Papers, 1979-1981 (Box 2)
- President's Papers, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
- President's Papers, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
- President's Report, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
- President's Report, 1982-1983 (Box 2)
- President's Report, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
- President's Report, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
- President's Report, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
- President's Book, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
- President's Notebook, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
- President's Notebook, 1989-1990 (Box 2)
- President's Notebook, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
- President's Notebook, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
- President's Notebook, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
- Presidents' Notebooks, 1995-1997 (Box 3)
- Presidents' Notebooks, 1995-1997 (Box 3)
- Presidents' Notebooks, 1995-1997 (Box 3)
- President's Notebook, 1997-1998 (Box 3)
- President's Notebook, 1997-1998 (Box 3)
- President's Notebook, 1998-1999 (Box 3)
- President's Notebook, 1998-1999 (Box 3)
- President's Notebook, 1999-2000 (Box 3)
- Newcomer's Club Membership, Project, and Officer Lists, 1939-1940 and 1968-1970 (Box 3)
- Newcomer's Club Sponsor Reports, 1951-1969 (Box 3)
- Newcomer's Club Reports, Minutes, and Project Notes, 1952-1972 (Box 3)
- Newcomer's Club Reports, Minutes, and Project Notes, 1952-1972 (Box 3)
- Newcomer's Club Reports, Minutes, and Project Notes, 1952-1972 (Box 3)
- Newcomer's Club Reports, Minutes, and Project Notes, 1952-1972 (Box 3)
- Campus and Newcomer's Clubs Printed Programs, 1954-1979 (Box 3)
- Newcomer's Club Clippings, 1955-1970 (Box 3)
- Newcomers Club Handbooks and Directories, 1959-1973 (Box 4)
- Newcomers Club Handbooks and Directories, 1959-1973 (Box 4)
- Newcomers Club Handbooks and Directories, 1959-1973 (Box 4)
- Newcomers Club Reports, Minutes, and Committee Notes, 1962-1968 (Box 4)
- Newcomers Club Reports, Minutes, and Committee Notes, 1962-1968 (Box 4)
- Newcomers Club Eligibility Lists, 1965-1969 (Box 4)
- Newcomers Welcome Package, ca. 1968 (Box 4)
- Newcomers Club Reports, Minutes, and Project Notes, 1969-1970 (Box 4)
- Committee for New Members Reports and Clippings, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
- Newcomers Welcome Package, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
- Newcomers Club History by Rheva Shyrock, 1971 (Box 4)
- Newcomers Welcome Package, 1972 (Box 4)
- New Member's Committee Records, 1972-1973 (Box 4)
- New Member's Committee, 1972-1977 (Box 4)
- New Member's Committee, 1972-1977 (Box 4)
- Executive Council and Board Notes, 1949-1962 (Box 4)
- Executive Council and Board Reports, 1962-1973 (Box 4)
- Board Minutes, Reports, and Documentation, 1972-1975 (Box 4)
- Officers, Executive Boards, and Committees, 1973-1979 (Box 5)
- Board Meeting Minutes, 1978-1985 (Box 5)
- Executive Board Materials, 1989-1992 (Box 5)
- Executive Board Materials, 1989-1992 (Box 5)
- Board Meeting Agendas and Notes, 1994-2009 (Box 5)
- Membership Committee Reports, 1950-1973 (Box 5)
- Membership Lists, Reports, and Notes, 1965-1978 (Box 5)
- Membership Lists, Reports, and Notes, 1965-1978 (Box 5)
- Dues Receipts, 1966-1968 (Box 5)
- Membership Cards, 1979-1981 (Box 5)
- Membership Lists, Reports, and Notes, 1980-1981 (Box 5)
- Membership Notebook, 1991-1992 (Box 5)
- Membership Notebook, 1997-1998 (Box 5)
- Membership Cards, undated (Box 5)
- President-Elect Notes and Records, 1976-1978 (Box 5)
- President-Elect Notes, 1978-1979 (Box 5)
- Past President's Books, 1981-1990 (Box 5)
- Past President's Books, 1981-1990 (Box 5)
- Past President's Books, 1981-1990 (Box 5)
- Past President's Books, 1981-1990 (Box 5)
- Past President's Books, 1981-1990 (Box 6)
- Vice President's Notebook, 1995-1997 (Box 6)
- President-Elect's Notebook, 1997-1999 (Box 6)
- President-Elect's Notebook, 1999-2004 (Box 6)
- Interest Groups Notes and Records, 1961-1989 (Box 6)
- Interest Groups Notes and Records, 1961-1989 (Box 6)
- Interest Group Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 6)
- Interest Groups Reports and Documentation, 1996-2001 (Box 6)
- Interest Groups Reports and Documentation, 1996-2001 (Box 6)
- Interest Groups Reports and Documentation, 1996-2001 (Box 6)
- Publications Committee Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 6)
- Publications Chairman Records, 1976-1979 (Box 6)
- Publications Notebook and Board Memoranda, 1994-1997 (Box 6)
- Publications Chair Notebook, 1997-2001 (Box 6)
- Newsletters Notebook, 1994-1998 (Box 6)
- Secretarial Records, 1962-1970 (Box 6)
- Secretary Records and Book, 1975-1980 (Box 6)
- Secretary's Notebook, 1992-2003 (Box 7)
- Secretary's Notebook, 1992-2003 (Box 7)
- Secretary's Notebook, 1999-2001 (Box 7)
- Policy Committee Reports, 1962-1975 (Box 7)
- Policy Committee Notes and Records, 1978-1986 (Box 7)
- Policy Committee Notes and Records, 1978-1986 (Box 7)
- Policy Notebook, 1993-1999 (Box 7)
- Policy Notebook, 1993-1999 (Box 7)
- Program Committee Reports, 1949-1970 (Box 7)
- Program Chairman Notes, 1974-1975 (Box 7)
- Program Committee Notebook, 1999-2001 (Box 7)
- Program Committee Notebook, 1999-2001 (Box 7)
- Social Committee Reports, 1943-1963 (Box 7)
- Social Chairman's Files, 1963-1973 (Box 7)
- Social Club Reports, 1978-1987 (Box 7)
- Social Chair's Notebook, 1996-1999 (Box 7)
- Nominating Committee Reports, 1959-1971 (Box 7)
- Nominating Committee Notebook, 1994-2003 (Box 7)
- Publicity Committee Reports, 1953-1970 (Box 7)
- Publicity Chair Records, 1980-1981 (Box 7)
- Lecture Series Programs, 1971-1972 to 1977-1978 (Box 8)
- Lecture Series Notes and Programs, 1971-1983 (Box 8)
- Lecture Series Introductions and Info, 1971-1983 (Box 8)
- Lecture Series Documentation, 1979-1980 (Box 8)
- Programs, Records, and Notes, 1980-1981 (Box 8)
- Programs, Records, and Notes, 1980-1981 (Box 8)
- Programs, Records, and Notes, 1980-1981 (Box 8)
- Music Appreciation and Study Group Notebook, 1949-1970 (Box 8)
- Music Appreciation and Study Group Notebook, 1949-1970 (Box 8)
- Music Appreciation and Study Group Notebook, 1949-1970 (Box 8)
- Music Group, 2005-2007 (Box 8)
- Faculty Dance/Christmas Party Records, 1986-1990 (Box 8)
- Faculty Dance/Christmas Party Records, 1986-1990 (Box 8)
- Computation Center Documentation, 1978-1980 (Box 8)
- Info about UNC Women's Club, 1968 (Box 8)
- Special Events Reports, 1989-1994 (Box 8)
- Study Group Chairman Reports, 1951-1972 (Box 8)
- Travel Group Member Lists, 1966-1970 (Box 8)
- Clippings and Publicity, 1946-1959 (Box 8)
- Clippings and Publicity, 1946-1959 (Box 8)
- Bulletins and Miscellaneous Documentation, 1951-1970 (Box 8)
- Brochures, 1955-1987 (Box 8)
- Clippings, 1958-1969 (Box 8)
- Clippings and Publicity, 1959-1983 (Box 8)
- Clippings and Publicity, 1959-1983 (Box 8)
- Clippings, 1962-1979 (Box 9)
- Clippings, Brochures, and Reports, 1971-1991 (Box 9)
- Clippings, Brochures, and Reports, 1971-1991 (Box 9)
- Newsletters, 1975-1977 (Box 9)
- Brochures, Memoranda, Clippings, and Misc, 1982-1991 (Box 9)
- Clippings and Programs, 1986-1989 (Box 9)
- Brochures, Memoranda, Clippings, and Misc, 1988-1989 (Box 9)
- Brochures, Memoranda, Clippings, and Misc, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
- Brochures, Memoranda, Clippings, and Misc, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
- Brochures, Memoranda, Clippings, and Misc, 1993-1994 (Box 9)
- Brochures, Memoranda, Clippings, and Misc, 1993-1994 (Box 9)
- Brochures, Memoranda, Clippings, and Misc, 1993-1994 (Box 9)
- Brochures, Memoranda, Clippings, and Misc, 1993-1994 (Box 9)
- Trinity College Campus Clubs Minutes and Notes, 1914-1918 (Box 9)
- Minutes and Committee Notes, 1933-35 and 1970 (Box 9)
- Minutes and Committee Notes, 1935-1937 (Box 9)
- Minutes and Committee Notes, 1937-1949 (Box 9)
- Annual and Business Meeting Reports, 1949-1970 (Box 9)
- Annual Reports, 1958-1974 (Box 9)
- Annual Reports, 1967-1970 (Box 9)
- Annual Reports, Notes, and Documentation, 1971-1980 (Box 10)
- Annual Reports, Notes, and Documentation, 1971-1980 (Box 10)
- Annual Reports, Notes, and Documentation, 1971-1980 (Box 10)
- Reports, Minutes, Brochures, and Misc, 1971-1992 (Box 10)
- Reports, Minutes, Brochures, and Misc, 1971-1992 (Box 10)
- Reports, Minutes, Brochures, and Misc, 1971-1992 (Box 10)
- Miscellaneous Reports and Documentation, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
- Annual Reports and Documentation, 1979-1986 (Box 10)
- Annual Reports and Documentation, 1979-1986 (Box 10)
- Annual Reports and Documentation, 1979-1986 (Box 10)
- Annual Reports and Documentation, 1979-1986 (Box 10)
- Minutes, Reports, and Notes, 1981-1983 (Box 10)
- Annual Reports, 1987-1999 (Box 10)
- Minutes, Memoranda, and Notes, 1993-2002 (Box 10)
- Reports, Minutes, Brochures, and Misc, 1994-1997 (Box 10)
- Reports, Minutes, Brochures, and Misc, 1994-1997 (Box 10)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1949-1961 (Box 10)
- Check Register, 1955-1969 (Box 10)
- Bank statements, 1956-1971 (Box 11)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1961-1976 (Box 11)
- Financial Reports and Event Info, 1971-1991 (Box 11)
- Receipt Book, 1971-1981 (Box 11)
- Assistant Treasurer Records, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
- Treasurer's Records, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
- Treasurer's Papers, 1979-1981 (Box 11)
- Treasurer's Papers, 1979-1981 (Box 11)
- Treasurer's Records and Receipts, 1976-1979 (Box 11)
- Treasurer's Records and Receipts, 1976-1979 (Box 11)
- Financial and Membership Records, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
- Financial Records and Treasurer's Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
- Financial Records and Treasurer's Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
- Tax Forms, 2006 (Box 11)
- Constitutions, 1914-1970 (Box 11)
- Framed Artwork Depicting Duke Chapel, c. 1938 (Box 11)
- Margaret Cannon's History of Campus Club, 1940 (Box 11)
- Bylaws, 1983-2007 (Box 11)
- History Project Research Materials, 1996-1998 (Box 11)
- History Project Research Materials, 1996-1998 (Box 11)
- History Project, 1996-1999 (Box 12)
- History Project, 1996-1999 (Box 12)
- History Project Interviews, 1997-1999 (Box 12)
- History Project Photographs and Captions, 1998 (Box 12)
- Letters from Soldiers Book, 1917 (Box 12)
- Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 12)
- Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 12)
- Correspondence, 1988 (Box 12)
- Scrapbook, 1956-1969 (Box 13)
- Scrapbook, 1961-1966 (Box 14)
- Scrapbook, 1963-1968 (Box 14)
- Newcomers Club Publicity Scrapbook, 1968-1970 (Box 14)
- Scrapbook, 1969-1976 (Box 15)
- Scrapbook Pages, 1970-1972 (Box 15)
- Lecture Series Scrapbook, 1979-1987 (Box 16)
- Lecture Series Scrapbook, 1987-2001 (Box 16)
- Scrapbook, 1981-1985 (Box 17)
- Scrapbook, 1985-1990 (Box 17)
- Treasurer Records, 1993-1995 (Box 18)
- Treasurer Records, 1998-1999 (Box 18)
- Financial and Miscellaneous Documentation, 1998-2004 (Box 18)
- Treasurer Records, 1999-2000 (Box 18)
- Treasurer Records, 2001-2002 (Box 18)
- Annual Reports and Financial Documentation, 2002-2004 (Box 18)
- Member Directories, 1999-2010 (2 Folders) (Box 18)
- Photographs from CC Board Lunch, 2004 (Box 18)
- Lecture Series Scrapbook, 1971-1976 (Box 19)
- Lecture Series Scrapbook, 1976-1979 (Box 19)
- Accession UA2012-0043 (unprocessed): includes binders of publicity material, including photographs and publications. (Box 20)
- Archives, Circa 2010 (Box 21)
- Brunk Auctions, March 10-11, 2012 (Box 21)
- Centennial Publicity, 2012-2014 (Box 21)
- Campus Club Centennial Tea, November 16, 2014 (Box 21)
- Directory, 2012 (Box 21)
- Gothic Gourmet, Circa 2010 (Box 21)
- Interest Groups (Chairs): Reports, 2002-2008 (Box 21)
- Interest Group Items Over Five Years Old, 2008-2010 (Box 21)
- Miscellaneous, 2004-2011 (Box 21)
- Mystery BC, 1996-2013 (Box 21)
- Newsletters, 2010-2011 (Box 21)
- Policies and Board Information, 2004-2008 (Box 21)
- President's Items, 2009-2010 (Box 21)
- President Elect, 2002-2009 (Box 21)
- Second VP Annual Report, 2012-2013 (Box 21)
- Secretary's Notebook, 2001-2010 (Box 21)
- Treasurer, 2006-2012 (Box 21)
- Wine Appreciation, 1985-2005 (Box 21)
- Morning Gourmet, 1995-2015 (Box 22)
- Gourmet Cooking, undated (Box 22)
- Around World, March 1997 (Box 22)
- New South, February 1997 (Box 22)
- APP, October 1996 (Box 22)
- Brunch, November 1996 (Box 22)
- Club Copy Recipes, 1992-1993 (Box 22)
- Extra Recipes, 1988-1993 (Box 22)
- Gourmet Group, undated (Box 22)
- Tea, undated (Box 22)
- President's book, 2011-2012 (Box 23)
- President's book, 2012-2013 (Box 23)
- Secretary's reports, 2010-2013 (Box 23)
- VP Social, 2003-2011 (Box 23)
- Interest group documents, 2011-2013 (Box 23)